&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：希望你对这个练习感觉很好，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So hopefully you feel pretty good about that exercise,
希望这是有意义的。
hopefully it made sense.
让我们潜入并尝试我们的手来定义这个对象是polyfill。
Let's dive in and try our hand at defining this object is polyfill.
所以第一，记住
So number one, remember,
我们需要一个if语句来检查Object.is是否尚未定义。
we want an if statement that checks to see that Object.is has not been defined.
现在，我将继续使用这个小速记，
Now, I'm gonna go ahead and use this little shorthand here,
这个布尔强制，我要说Object.is的否定。
this Boolean coercion, I'm gonna say that the negate of Object.is.
因此，如果定义了Object.is，
So if Object.is has been defined,
定义它的唯一方式是作为函数。
the only way that it ever gets defined is as a function.
所以它肯定在真实的清单上，如果我否定它，并且
So it's definitely on the truthy list, and if I negate it, and
如果它不在那里，它肯定是未定义的。
if it's not there, it's definitely undefined.
所以对我来说，这是我可以接受布尔强制的地方之一
So to me, this is one of those places where I'm okay with the Boolean coercion
因为，嘿，我们只检查未定义的还是完全存在的。
because, hey, we're only checking either undefined versus totally present.
在这两者之间真的没有任何地方。
There's really nowhere in between.
所以我们说如果不是Object.is，我会把这个或true扔进去
So we're saying if not Object.is, and I'm gonna throw in this or true for
刚才，只是为了确保我们确实在运行我们的函数。
just now, just so we make sure that we're actually running our function.
我第一次做这个练习的时候，我犯了这个错误，而且
The first time I made this exercise, I made that mistake, and
我搞不懂为什么事情不能正常工作，[笑]或者
I couldn't figure out why things weren't working, [LAUGH] or
为什么即使我破解了代码，事情还是可以工作的。
why things were still working even when I had broken code.
所以很容易犯这些错误。
So it's easy to make those mistakes.
好的，所以我们将定义一个，Object.is=function，和
All right, so we're gonna define one, Object.is = function, and
如果我能输入的话，我就把它命名为Object.is。
I'll just name it Object.is, if I could ever type.
它需要两个参数，所以我称之为x和y。
And it's gonna take two parameters, so I'll call it x and y.
如果你感觉更好，你可以称之为v1和v2。
You could call it v1 and v2 if you feel better about that.
同样，Object.的工作本质上是三重等于，
Again, the job of Object.is is essentially the triple equals,
但它也不需要在负0和NaN的情况下存在。
but also it needs to not lie in the cases of negative 0 and NaN.
所以这里有一点细微的差别，
So there's a little bit of nuance here,
我碰巧已经知道了，所以我就直接说了。
which I happened to already know about, so I'll just jump to it.
我们想要得到一个指示器，如果你愿意的话，一个真的假的，
We wanna go ahead and get an indicator, a true false if you will,
x是否为负0，y是否为负0。
of whether x is a negative 0 and whether y is a negative 0.
所以我把它叫做xNegZero；y负零，
So I'm gonna call it xNegZero; y negative zero,
这些只是我在这里赋值的变量。
those are just gonna be variables that I assign to here in a moment.
我要给它们赋值的是测试值的结果
And what I'm gonna assign them is the result of testing a value for
它的负零点。
its negative zeroness.
所以我要定义一个小帮手
So I'm gonna define a little helper for
我自己弄清楚某件事是否为负0。
myself to figure out if something is a negative 0.
我想知道你们中有没有人能想出一种方法来做到这一点，而不需要
I wonder if any of you were able to come up with a way of doing that without
内置对象是？
the built in object.is?
有人吗？
Anyone?
&gt；&gt；学生：几周前我偶然发现了它。
&gt;&gt; Student: I stumbled across it a couple weeks ago accidentally.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，那么你-&gt；&gt；学生：所以我作弊了。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, so you- &gt;&gt; Student: So I cheated.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：你碰巧已经看过了，好吧，酷。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You happened to have already seen it, okay, cool.
那我们该怎么做？
Well how would we do that?
这是一个有点棘手，所以如果你没有得到它，不要感觉不好。
This one's a little tricky, so if you didn't get it, don't feel bad.
但是如果你考虑一个负0的值，
But if you think about a value that is negative 0,
关于我们可以用0做的操作，我们知道什么？
what do we know about operations that we can do with 0?
所以如果你说，取一个负的0，然后加上一个0？
So if you say, take a negative 0, and you add a 0 to it?
嗯，如果你这样做了，你知道你只会得到一个普通的0。
Well, if you do that you know you're just gonna get a regular 0.
如果你取一个负的0，然后减去一个0，就不会有其他的事情发生了，
If you take a negative 0 and you subtract a 0 from it nothing else is gonna happen,
它仍然是负0。
it's still gonna be a negative 0.
所以加法和减法不会有帮助。
So adding and subtracting aren't gonna help.
但组织呢？
But what about division?
我们知道，例如，1除以0就是无穷大。
We know that for example, 1 divided by 0 gives us infinity.
你认为1乘以0会给我们带来什么？
What do you think one 1 by negative 0 would give us?
&gt；&gt；Student2：负无穷大。
&gt;&gt; Student2: Negative infinity.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：负无穷大。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Negative infinity.
所以有一种方法可以测试我们是否有负0，
So there's a way of testing if we have a negative 0,
唯一可以得到负无穷大的方法是，如果我们有一个负的0。
the only way we could get negative infinity is if we had a negative 0.
也许不是唯一的方法，但这就是我们要做的。
Maybe not the only way but that's the way we're gonna do it.
所以我会说如果NegZero接受一个值，我会说，首先，
So I'm gonna say if NegZero take in a value, and I'm gonna say, first of all,
我们需要确保它是两个0中的一个，因为如果它是无穷大，
we need to make sure it's one of the two 0 because if it was infinity,
这会给我们一个假阳性。
that would give us a false positive here.
所以我们会说，如果v是两个0中的一个，
So we'll say, if v is one of the two 0s,
我们可以使用双等号或三等号。
which we can either use the double equals or the triple equals.
在这种情况下，他们将不会在两者之间有任何区别。
In this case, they would not have any distinction between the two.
所以如果是两个0中的一个
So if it's one of the two 0,
然后我们会说
and, and then we're gonna say
(1/v)=-无穷大。
(1/v) == -Infinity.
这就是我们如何知道-&gt；&gt；学生3：这是不是一个常数
That's how we could know- &gt;&gt; Student3: Was that a constant in
JavaScript？
JavaScript?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：infinity是内置的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Infinity is a built-in.
&gt；&gt；学生3：真的吗？&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，
&gt;&gt; Student3: Really? &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yep,
这是一个内置的标识符。
it's a built-in identifier.
学生3：好的。
&gt;&gt; Student3: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：1除以v会得到负无穷大，如果和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So 1 divided by v would give us negative infinity, if and
仅当v为负0时。
only if v was negative 0.
同样，这个检查的原因是1除以负无穷大，
Again, the reason for this check is 1 divided by negative infinity,
也会给出负无穷大。
would also give negative infinity.
[笑]所以，我们不想在这里有任何误报。
[LAUGH] So, we don't wanna have any false positives here.
好的，这就是我们如何检查x和y是否为负0，
Okay, so that's how we're going to check if x and y are negative 0s,
我们要称之为小公用事业。
we're gonna call that little utility.
所以我们会说，如果isItNegZero(X)，并且
So we'll say, if isItNegZero(x), and
然后我们说如果isItNegZero(Y)。
then we'll say if isItNegZero(y).
现在，我们要做的第一件事是如果x或
Now, the first thing we wanna do is if either x or
Y是负0，然后我们要检查它们是否都是。
y is a negative 0 then we're gonna check if both of them are.
但我们需要先检查一下我们是否在处理这个案子
But we need to first check if we're dealing with the case that
它们中的任何一个都是负0。
either one of them is the negative 0.
因为如果它们中的任何一个都是负0，
Because if either one of them is negative 0,
我们知道三重相等将会说谎，所以我们不能允许这种情况发生。
we know that the triple equals is gonna lie, so we can't allow that to occur.
所以我们会说，如果(xNegZero或yNegZero)，
So we're gonna say, if (xNegZero or yNegZero),
这将是我们的条件之一，我们会处理如何处理它。
that's gonna be one of our conditions, and we'll handle what to do with that.
现在，如果不是这样的话，下一件事就是
Now, if that's not the case, the next thing that
我们需要检查x和y是否都是nans。
we need to check is if both the x and the y are NaNs.
大家都跟我一起吗？
Everybody with me?
如果他们两个都是nans，那么我们想返回真的，
If both of them are NaNs, then we wanna return true,
因为我们知道这就是三重等于会返回false的情况，
because we know that's the case where triple equals would return a false false,
如果你愿意，它会撒谎说假。
if you will, it would lie and say false.
因此，我们需要另一个实用程序来检查NAS。
So we need another utility for checking for NaNs.
您可以只使用number.isNaN，但是
You could just use number.isNaN, but
自述文件建议，也许可以尝试一下你的手来想出它。
the README suggested maybe try your hand to coming up with it.
有没有人想出一种测试的方法
Did anyone come up with a way of testing for testing for
NaN没有内置的实用程序？
NaN without the built-in utilities?
几周前你也看过那个[笑]吗？
Did you also see that one [LAUGH] a couple of weeks ago?
好吧，你想到了什么？
Okay, what did you come up with?
&gt；&gt；学生：有点像Jenky。
&gt;&gt; Student: It's kinda jenky.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它是什么？&gt；&gt；学生：但它是一个检查是否
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What is it? &gt;&gt; Student: But it's an if that checks if
param1不等于param1或param2不等于param2。
param1 is not equal to param1 or param2 is not equal to param2.
凯尔·辛普森：好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Student：然后在里面返回param1的类型是number和
&gt;&gt; Student: And then inside there returns type of param1 is number and
param2的类型是number，那么它们是唯一不相等的数字
type of param2 is number, then they're the only numbers that are not equal
对自己-&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：好的。
to themselves- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay.
&gt；&gt；学生：[相声]nans。
&gt;&gt; Student: [CROSSTALK] NaNs.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：你在正确的轨道上。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You're on the right track.
我认为我们甚至可以做得更简单，你在正确的轨道上。
I think we can even do this simpler, you're on the right track.
这里的具体技巧是NaN是
The specific trick here is that NaN is the only value in
JavaScript中不等于自身的存在。
existence in JavaScript that's not equal to itself.
所以如果我传入一个NaN，它将不等于它本身
So if I pass in a NaN, it will be not equal to itself and
其他一切都会失败。
everything else that would fail.
所以我们可以简单地说，v不等于它本身。
So we can simply say, v not equal to itself.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：而NaN是唯一一个从那里返回真的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And NaN is the only one that would return true from there.
所以我要测试一下
So I'm going to test,
如果(isItNaN(X)&amp；&amp；
if (isItNaN(x) &amp;&amp;
isItNaN(Y)。
isItNaN(y)).
如果是这样，我们肯定知道返回真，因为它们都是Nans，
And if that's the case, we definitely know return true, cuz they're both NaNs,
这就是我们想要说出真相的情况。
and this is the case where we wanna tell the truth.
如果这两种情况都不是这样，那么我们真正需要做的就是
And if neither one of those too is the case then really all we need to do is to
进一步的三重相等。
further the triple equals.
因此我们只返回x=y；。
So we simply return x === y;.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们在这里处理这个特殊的情况。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's handle this particular case up here.
如果他们中的一个或两个我们还不确定，但是
If one or both of them we're not sure yet, but
我们知道其中至少有一个是负0。
we know at least one of them is a negative 0.
那么我们怎么知道我们是否应该返回true呢？
Then how do we know if we should return true or not?
好吧，只有在它们都是负0的情况下。
Well, only if both of them are negative 0.
因此，我们可以在这里简单地说return xNegZero&amp；&amp；yNegZero；。
So we can simply say here return xNegZero &amp;&amp; yNegZero;.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我已经知道的一点预优化
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So the little pre-optimization that I already knew about
就是我需要检查两次所以我继续
was that I was gonna need to check it twice so I went ahead and
将其缓存到变量中，而不是通过函数调用检查两次。
cashed it into a variable instead of checking it twice with the function call.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：对解决方案文件进行双重检查，正如您在这里看到的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Double checking against the solution file, as you see over here,
我写的几乎是一样的。
and I've written it almost the same.
我只想把我刚写的这段代码
I'm gonna just take this code that I just wrote
这里，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：和
here, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And
我有一个小环境。
I have a little environment.
这个程序叫做Run JS，它就像一个执行东西的控制台，
This program's called Run JS, which is like a console that executes stuff,
不是十全十美，但相当不错。
it's not perfect but it's pretty good.
所以我要把这段代码放到这里并运行它。
So I'm gonna drop this code into here and run it.
我们应该看到所有的真相，我们做到了。
And we should see all trues and we do.